"dota"
{
"TitleText"	"{s:TitleTextVar}"
"[english]TitleText"	"{s:TitleTextVar}"
"BodyText"	"{s:BodyTextVar}"
"[english]BodyText"	"{s:BodyTextVar}"
"ProgressText"	"{s:ProgressTextVar}"
"[english]ProgressText"	"{s:ProgressTextVar}"
"EndScreenClose"	"終了"
"[english]EndScreenClose"	"EXIT"
"ag_alert_InvulnerabilityTitle"	"戦闘一時停止"
"[english]ag_alert_InvulnerabilityTitle"	"Combat Paused"
"ag_info_PreGamePrepTitle"	"計画：勝利への鍵"
"[english]ag_info_PreGamePrepTitle"	"Planning: The Key to Victory"
"ag_info_PreGamePrepBody"	"Dota では、計画はスキルと同様に重要です。一流のチームはお互いに補完しあうヒーローを選択し、攻撃されてるときにはサポートしあい、ともに目標を達成しようとします。今回はこれらを学びます。今は、一つの役割を上手くこなすことに集中します。"
"[english]ag_info_PreGamePrepBody"	"In Dota, planning is just as important as skill. The best teams choose heroes which complement each other, support each other when under attack, and try to take objectives together. These are things you will learn with time. For now, we'll focus on doing well in one role."
"ag_info_YourRoleTitle"	"あなたの役割：力を集めて、敵を破壊する"
"[english]ag_info_YourRoleTitle"	"Your Role: Gather Power, then Destroy the Enemy"
"ag_info_YourRoleBody"	"このマッチでは、ゲーム中盤から後半にかけての成長に集中します。\n\n少しのレベルとアイテムで戦闘において強力となり、タワーを素早く破壊できるようになります。\n\nあなたのチームメイトをコントロールするボットはあなたの行動のサポートを行います。"
"[english]ag_info_YourRoleBody"	"In this match you will focus on building toward Mid to Late Game power.\n\nWith a few levels and items you will be powerful in fights and able to destroy Towers quickly.\n\nThe bots which control your teammates will try to work around what you do."
"ag_info_GamePlanTitle"	"ゲームプラン"
"[english]ag_info_GamePlanTitle"	"Game Plan"
"ag_info_GamePlanBody"	"1) 開始アイテムを購入して準備\n2) レーンで生き抜き、ゴールドと経験値を獲得\n3) 追加ゴールドを獲得するためにクリープをラストヒット\n4) ゲーム初期アイテムを購入してヒーローを強化\n5) チームメイトとともに敵タワーを破壊\n6) 敵バラックを破壊\n7) 相手の Ancient を破壊してマッチに勝利"
"[english]ag_info_GamePlanBody"	"1) Prepare by purchasing your Starting Items\n2) Survive in your lane to earn Gold and Experience\n3) Strike the Last Hit on creeps to earn additional gold\n4) Buy Early Game Items to strengthen your hero\n5) Destroy enemy Towers with teammates\n6) Destroy the enemy Barracks\n7) Destroy the enemy Ancient to win the match"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaTitle"	"アビリティとアイテムビルド：攻撃とサバイバル"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Damage and Survival"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaBody"	"このマッチでは、アビリティとアイテムビルドの順番は予め決められています。\n\nゲームを進めるにしたがって、アイテムがあなたの攻撃力を高めたり、ターゲットの間を飛び跳ねてあなたの体力を回復することが出来るようになるので、敵へ突撃し、近くの敵を破壊することの出来る強力なアルティメットアビリティを放つときに役立ちます。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will enable you to deal damaging attacks which also heal you as they bounce between targets. This will help you to survive as you charge enemies and launch your powerful ultimate ability, which can destroy nearby foes."
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenTitle"	"アビリティとアイテムビルド：耐久性と攻撃力"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Durability and Damage"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenBody"	"このマッチではアビリティとアイテムビルドの順番が予め決められています。\n\nゲームを進めるに連れてアイテムがあなたのアーマーと攻撃力を増強し、敵との距離を縮めて倒せるようになります。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will increase your armor and attack damage, allowing you to close the distance to your enemy and then cut them down."
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaTitle"	"アビリティとアイテムビルド：頻繁にキャストするためのマナ"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Mana to Cast Abilities Often"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaBody"	"このマッチではアビリティとアイテムビルドの順番が予め決められています。\n\nゲームが進むに連れてアイテムから追加のマナやマナ回復を受け、非常に強力でマナ消費量の多い Lina のスペルをより頻繁に撃てる用になります。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will grant you additional mana and mana regeneration, making it possible to cast Lina's extremely powerful and costly spells more often."
"ag_info_LaningTitle"	"ゲーム序盤：クリープからゴールドを獲得して生き抜く"
"[english]ag_info_LaningTitle"	"Early Game: Survive While Earning Gold from Creeps"
"ag_info_LaningBody"	"回復パワーを持ちあなたをサポートしてくれる Dazzle と一緒にボトムレーンに行きます。\n\n今の最優先事項はゴールドを獲得し、何よりも生き抜くことです！\n\n死ぬことは厄介なだけでなく、あなたを倒した敵を強力にして、あなたはゴールドの一部を失ってしまいます。"
"[english]ag_info_LaningBody"	"You will be going to the Bottom Lane and partnered with Dazzle, who will support you with his healing powers.\n\nYour top priorities for now are to earn gold and above all, SURVIVE!\n\nDying isn't just inconvenient; enemies will gain power for killing you, and you will lose a portion of your gold."
"ag_info_LaningIntroTitle"	"ゲーム序盤：戦闘開始"
"[english]ag_info_LaningIntroTitle"	"Early Game: The Battle Begins"
"ag_info_LaningIntroBody"	"クリープのウェーブが間もなく発生します。彼らについて戦場へ行きましょう。\n\n敵からの攻撃を受けないように、クリープの前にはでないようにし、クリープのウェーブが全滅したら 、下がって次のクリープウェーブに合流してください。"
"[english]ag_info_LaningIntroBody"	"A wave of creeps is about to spawn. Follow them into battle and support them with your attacks.\n\nCreeps automatically march toward the enemy base, attacking any enemy units or buildings they encounter.\n\nWhen a wave of creeps dies, back up and regroup with the next creep wave."
"ag_info_CoreItemsTitle"	"ゲーム序盤：アイテム購入"
"[english]ag_info_CoreItemsTitle"	"Early Game: Purchase Items"
"ag_info_CoreItemsBody"	"ラストヒットがかなり上手くなってきました。\n\nゴールドを稼ぎ続けてゲーム序盤アイテムを全て購入しよう。\n\nこれらアイテムは、ゲーム中盤に戦場を自由に動き回るようになる前に、効果的な戦士へを成長するのを助けます。"
"[english]ag_info_CoreItemsBody"	"You're getting better at striking Last Hits.\n\nContinue earning gold and purchase all of your Early Game Items.\n\nThese items will help you become an effective warrior before you begin to move around the battlefield in the Mid Game."
"ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsTitle"	"ゲーム序盤：アイテム購入"
"[english]ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsTitle"	"Early Game: Purchase Items"
"ag_info_TakeObjectivesTitle"	"ゲーム中盤：タワーを破壊し勝利へと突き進む"
"[english]ag_info_TakeObjectivesTitle"	"Mid Game: Destroy Towers and Push Toward Victory"
"ag_info_TakeObjectivesBody"	"ゲーム序盤用のアイテムを既に入手済みなので、これからは目標に集中して3レーンにある全てのタワーを破壊しよう。\n\nゴールドと経験値の獲得はもちろん重要ですが、今は戦場を動き回ってチームメイトと共に敵のタワーを破壊しよう。"
"[english]ag_info_TakeObjectivesBody"	"Now that you have your Early Game Items, it's time to focus on objectives, and destroy the Towers in all three lanes.\n\nIt's still important for you to gain gold and experience, but now you should begin moving around the battlefield to join your teammates and destroy enemy Towers."
"ag_info_HighgroundTitle"	"ゲーム後半: 敵ベースへの攻撃"
"[english]ag_info_HighgroundTitle"	"Late Game: Assaulting the Enemy Base"
"ag_info_HighgroundBody"	"敵のベースを攻撃する時が来ました！ベース内側のそれぞれのレーンにタワーと1組のバラックがあります。敵のバラックを破壊すると同列レーン内のあなたのクリープが強化されます。\n\n敵の Ancient を攻撃するにはまず、それを保護している2つのタワーを破壊しなければなりません。敵の Ancient を破壊して勝利を掴み取ろう。"
"[english]ag_info_HighgroundBody"	"It's time to attack the enemy base! Inside, you'll find a Tower and pair of Barracks in each lane. Destroying an enemy Barracks will strengthen your creeps in that lane.\n\nTo attack the enemy's Ancient, first destroy the two Towers guarding it. Destroy the enemy's Ancient to win the match."
"ag_info_FoundARuneTitle"	"ルーン：2分毎に様々なボーナス"
"[english]ag_info_FoundARuneTitle"	"Runes: Various Bonuses Every Two Minutes"
"ag_info_FoundARuneBody"	"ルーンに近づいています。ルーンにはいくつかの種類があり、有効化するとそれぞれ特徴的なボーナスが得られます。\n\n2分ごとに新しいルーン川の南北に出現します"
"[english]ag_info_FoundARuneBody"	"You are approaching a Rune. There are several types of Runes, and each provides a significant bonus to your hero when activated.\n\nNew Runes will appear at the north and south ends of the river every two minutes."
"ag_info_RoshanTitle"	"Roshan と Aegis of the Immortal"
"[english]ag_info_RoshanTitle"	"Roshan & Aegis of the Immortal"
"ag_info_RoshanBody"	"Roshan は非常に強力な中立の怪物です。チーム一丸となって討伐すると、Aegis of the Immortal をドロップします。\n\nAegis を持っている状態でヒーローが死ぬと、その場所ですぐに復活を遂げます。\n\nRoshan は討伐から8分から11分で再出現します。"
"[english]ag_info_RoshanBody"	"Roshan is an extremely powerful neutral monster. If a team gathers and slays him, he will leave behind the Aegis of the Immortal.\n\nIf a hero holding the Aegis dies, they will immediately revive at the location of their death.\n\nOnce killed, Roshan will reappear in his pit after eight to eleven minutes."
"ag_info_CreepCampsTitle"	"ジャングルクリープのキャンプ: その他のパワー源"
"[english]ag_info_CreepCampsTitle"	"Jungle Creep Camps: Another Source of Power"
"ag_info_CreepCampsBody"	"レーンの間にある森はジャングルと呼ばれます。ジャングル内には中立クリープモンスターのキャンプがいくつかあります。\n\nあなたのヒーローが十分に強力になったら、これらのクリープを倒してゴールドと経験値を稼ぐことができます。キャンプは空になってから1分後に復元されます。"
"[english]ag_info_CreepCampsBody"	"The forests between the lanes are called the Jungle. Throughout the Jungle are several camps filled with neutral creep monsters.\n\nIf your hero is powerful enough, these creeps can provide an alternative way to earn gold and experience. Empty creep camps refill every minute."
"ag_info_SideShopTitle"	"サイドショップ：戦場での必需品"
"[english]ag_info_SideShopTitle"	"The Side Shop: Supplies in the Field"
"ag_info_SideShopBody"	"トップレーンとボトムレーンの川付近にサイドショップがあります。\n\nいくつかの種類のブーツの部品、戦場をテレポートする為の Town Portal Scrolls などゲーム初期に役立つ様々なアイテムを購入できます。"
"[english]ag_info_SideShopBody"	"Side Shops can be found just outside of the Top and Bottom Lanes near the river.\n\nThey sell various items useful in the Early Game, including the components for several types of boots, as well as Town Portal Scrolls which are used to teleport around the battlefield."
"ag_info_VictoryTitle"	"勝利！"
"[english]ag_info_VictoryTitle"	"Victory!"
"ag_info_VictoryBody"	"おめでとうございます！本当のマッチへ参加する準備が整いました。\n\n他のヒーローについて学びたかったり、このヒーローの練習をもっとしたかったら、「ヒーロー」タブを開いて「デモヒーロー」機能を使ってください。\n\nDota はフレンドとのプレイが最も楽しめますので、パーティを作ってお楽しみください！"
"[english]ag_info_VictoryBody"	"Congratulations! You are now ready for a real match.\n\nIf you would like to learn about other heroes, or practice more with this one, visit the \"Heroes\" tab and use the \"Demo Hero\" feature.\n\nDota is best enjoyed with friends, so form a party and have fun!"
"ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsTitle"	"大量のタワーダメージ"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsTitle"	"Excessive Tower Damage"
"ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsBody"	"タワーからのダメージは致命的です！\n\n一度下がり、あなたの代わりに味方クリープにその攻撃を受けてもらいましょう。"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsBody"	"Towers are deadly!\n\nRetreat and let your creeps suffer its attacks instead."
"ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsTitle"	"大量のクリープダメージ"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsTitle"	"Excessive Creep Damage"
"ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsBody"	"クリープから大量のダメージを受けています！\n\nクリープは最初に直面した敵を攻撃しますが、あなたがヒーローか敵チームを攻撃するとあなたが攻撃対象となってしまいます。"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsBody"	"You are taking a lot of damage from Creeps!\n\nThough creeps will attack the first enemy they encounter, they will switch to attacking you if you attack a hero on their team."
"ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsTitle"	"ゴールドを使おう"
"[english]ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsTitle"	"Spend your gold"
"ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsBody"	"アイテムのクイックバイは{g:dota_key:keyname} を押してください。"
"[english]ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsBody"	"Press {g:dota_key:keyname} to buy a Quick Buy item."
"ag_alert_LowHealthTitle"	"ヘルスが低い"
"[english]ag_alert_LowHealthTitle"	"Low Health"
"ag_alert_LowHealthBody"	"ヘルスが下がっています。\n\nHealing Salve か Tango を使って回復してください。"
"[english]ag_alert_LowHealthBody"	"Your health is low.\n\nUse a Healing Salve or a Tango to heal."
"ag_alert_FirstPurchaseTitle"	"レーンでの購入：いつでもクイックバイ"
"[english]ag_alert_FirstPurchaseTitle"	"Buying in Lane: Quick Buy at any Time"
"ag_alert_FirstPurchaseBody"	"スクリーン下方にクイックバイトレーを用意し、必要なアイテムをここに入れておきました。購入するには中のアイテムを右クリックするか、{g:dota_key:keyname}を押してください。\n\n戦場にいる間、ベースショップから購入したアイテムはスタッシュに保管されます。 {g:dota_key:keyname2}を押すと、チームのクーリエがアイテムをスタッシュから運んでくれます。"
"[english]ag_alert_FirstPurchaseBody"	"We have placed the items you will need in the Quick Buy tray near the bottom of the screen. Purchase items by right-clicking on them there, or by pressing {g:dota_key:keyname}.\n\nItems purchased from your base's shop while you are in the field are placed in your Stash. You can have your team's Courier deliver items from your Stash by pressing {g:dota_key:keyname2}."
"ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsTitle"	"ゴールドを使おう！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsTitle"	"Spend your gold!"
"ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsBody"	"未使用のゴールドが大量にあります。何か買いましょう。死ぬとゴールドを失うことを忘れないで下さい！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsBody"	"You have a lot of unspent gold. Buy something. Remember, you lose gold when you die!"
"ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsTitle"	"スタッシュ内のアイテム"
"[english]ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsTitle"	"Items in Your Stash"
"ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsBody"	"{g:dota_key:keyname} を押すと、チームのクーリエがスタッシュからアイテムを運んでくれます。"
"[english]ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsBody"	"Press {g:dota_key:keyname} to have the items in your Stash delivered by your team's courier."
"ag_alert_CanLevelUpTitle"	"レベルアップ"
"[english]ag_alert_CanLevelUpTitle"	"Level Up"
"ag_alert_CanLevelUpBody"	"新アビリティを学ぶか、既に学んだアビリティを強化しよう。"
"[english]ag_alert_CanLevelUpBody"	"Learn a new ability, or strengthen an existing one."
"ag_alert_ForceLevelUpTitle"	"レベルアップ！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForceLevelUpTitle"	"Level Up!"
"ag_alert_ForceLevelUpBody"	"レベルポイントを使い切っていません。スキルにポイントを使用しましょう。"
"[english]ag_alert_ForceLevelUpBody"	"You haven't used all of your Level Points. Add points to a skill."
"ag_alert_BehindOnTowersTitle"	"タワーの破壊"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnTowersTitle"	"Destroy Towers"
"ag_alert_BehindOnTowersBody"	"敵に破壊される前に、敵タワーを破壊しましょう！"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnTowersBody"	"Destroy enemy Towers before the enemy can destroy yours!"
"ag_alert_BehindOnGoldTitle"	"ゴールドが足りない"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnGoldTitle"	"Behind on Gold"
"ag_alert_BehindOnGoldBody"	"クリープをラストヒットしてゴールドをもっと稼ぎましょう。"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnGoldBody"	"Last Hit more creeps to catch up on gold."
"ag_alert_BehindOnExpTitle"	"経験値が足りない"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnExpTitle"	"Behind on Experience"
"ag_alert_BehindOnExpBody"	"戦闘の近くで経験値を稼ぎましょう。"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnExpBody"	"Stay near combat to earn experience."
"ag_alert_UseSalveTitle"	"怪我をしている"
"[english]ag_alert_UseSalveTitle"	"You Are Hurt"
"ag_alert_UseSalveBody"	"Healing Salve を使って回復してください。使用中ダメージを受けると効果が途切れてしまいます。"
"[english]ag_alert_UseSalveBody"	"Use a Healing Salve to heal. Taking damage cancels the effect."
"ag_alert_UseClarityTitle"	"マナの回復"
"[english]ag_alert_UseClarityTitle"	"Restore Mana"
"ag_alert_UseClarityBody"	"Clarity を使ってマナを回復させましょう。使用中ダメージを受けると効果が途切れてしまいます。"
"[english]ag_alert_UseClarityBody"	"Use a Clarity to restore mana. Taking damage cancels the effect."
"ag_alert_RespawnTitle"	"復活"
"[english]ag_alert_RespawnTitle"	"Respawn"
"ag_alert_RespawnBody"	"あなたのヒーローが間もなく復活します。\n\n直ぐに戦闘準備を整えてください！"
"[english]ag_alert_RespawnBody"	"Your hero will respawn soon.\n\nTry to get back into the action quickly!"
"ag_alert_TangoUsageTitle"	"Tangos"
"[english]ag_alert_TangoUsageTitle"	"Tangos"
"ag_alert_TangoUsageBody"	"Tangos を使って木を食べると、時間をかけてヘルスを回復できます。\n\nTango を使うには、食べる木を左クリックしてください。"
"[english]ag_alert_TangoUsageBody"	"Tangos let you eat a tree to heal your hero over time.\n\nLeft-click on a tree to use a tango."
"ag_alert_SalveUsageTitle"	"Healing Salve"
"[english]ag_alert_SalveUsageTitle"	"Healing Salve"
"ag_alert_SalveUsageBody"	"Healing Salves を使うと対象のヒーロー（左クリック）を素早く回復できます。\n\n使用中にダメージを受けると、効果はキャンセルされてしまいます。"
"[english]ag_alert_SalveUsageBody"	"Healing Salves can quickly heal the hero you target (left-click).\n\nTaking damage will cancel the effect."
"ag_alert_ClarityUsageTitle"	"Clarity"
"[english]ag_alert_ClarityUsageTitle"	"Clarity"
"ag_alert_ClarityUsageBody"	"Clarity はターゲットの（左クリック）ヒーローのマナをゆっくりと回復させます。\n\n使用中ダメージを受けると、効果は止まってしまいます。"
"[english]ag_alert_ClarityUsageBody"	"Clarity slowly regenerates the mana of the hero you target (left click).\n\nTaking damage will cancel the effect."
"ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageBody"	"痛っ！タワーから大量のダメージを受けています！\n\nタワーが他の目標へ攻撃を開始するまで下がってください。"
"[english]ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageBody"	"Ouch! You are taking a lot of damage from the Tower!\n\nBack up until the Tower begins to attack something else."
"ag_alert_DeathTitle"	"死亡と復活"
"[english]ag_alert_DeathTitle"	"Death & Respawning"
"ag_alert_DeathBody"	"死亡すると、ゴールドの一部を失い、あなたを倒したヒーローは経験値を獲得してより強力になります。\n\n死亡期間が終了するとチームの泉で復活をとげます。死亡タイマーは、スクリーン上部のヒーローの肖像の下に表示されます。\n\nレベルが高いほど、死亡期間は長くなります。"
"[english]ag_alert_DeathBody"	"When you die, you lose a portion of your gold, and the hero or heroes responsible for your death earn experience to become stronger.\n\nYou will respawn at your team's fountain when your death timer ends. You can see your death timer beneath your hero's portrait at the top of the screen.\n\nEach level gained increases how long a hero remains dead."
"ag_alert_FountainTitle"	"泉：回復の源"
"[english]ag_alert_FountainTitle"	"The Fountain: A Source of Healing"
"ag_alert_FountainBody"	"死亡後、チームの泉から復活します。泉に戻るとヘルスとマナを素早く回復することが出来ます。"
"[english]ag_alert_FountainBody"	"After death, your hero will respawn at their team's fountain. Returning to the Fountain will quickly restore your health and mana."
"ag_alert_ScrollTitle"	"Town Portal Scrolls: 戦場をテレポートで移動しよう"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollTitle"	"Town Portal Scrolls: Teleport Around the Battlefield"
"ag_alert_ScrollBody"	"戦場を素早く移動することは重要です。\n\nTown Portal Scrolls はショップから購入でき、使用すると味方のタワーあるいは建造物間をテレポートすることができます。\n\n使用するには、左クリックし、ミニマップ内で移動先の建造物を左クリックで指定してください。"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollBody"	"Moving around the battlefield quickly is important.\n\nTown Portal Scrolls can be purchased from the shop, and allow you to teleport to an allied Tower or other building.\n\nTo use a Scroll, left-click on the item, then left-click on an allied building on the minimap to teleport there."
"ag_alert_ScrollUsageTitle"	"Town Portal Scroll"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollUsageTitle"	"Town Portal Scroll"
"ag_alert_ScrollUsageBody"	"Town Portal Scroll を買って使おう。Town Portal Scroll を左クリックしてから、ミニマップ内で移動先のタワーあるいは建造物を左クリックしてください。"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollUsageBody"	"Purchase and use a Town Portal Scroll. To use the Scroll, left-click on the item, then left-click on any allied building on the minimap to teleport there."
"ag_alert_SecretShopTitle"	"シークレットショップ：ここでしか手に入らないアイテム"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopTitle"	"Secret Shop: Items not available elsewhere"
"ag_alert_SecretShopBody"	"シークレットショップでしか購入できないアイテムがあります。シークレットショップから遠い場所でこれらのアイテムを買おうとすると、どこへ行けば買えるかお知らせされます。"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopBody"	"Some items can only be purchased from a Secret Shop. If you try to buy one of these items while out of range of a Secret Shop, a marker will appear to tell you where to go."
"ag_alert_SecretShopFoundTitle"	"シークレットショップ: 実は秘密じゃありません"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopFoundTitle"	"The Secret Shop: Not Actually a Secret"
"ag_alert_SecretShopFoundBody"	"シークレットショップへようこそ。\n\n川の両側にシークレットショップがあり、買えるアイテムは同じです。チームに関係なく使用できます。"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopFoundBody"	"Welcome to the Secret Shop.\n\nThere is a Secret Shop on both sides of the river, and both sell the same items. Either team can use either Secret Shop."
"ag_detail_BaseStatsTitle"	"アビリティ: 属性 - メイン数値を上昇"
"[english]ag_detail_BaseStatsTitle"	"Ability: Attributes - Increase Your Primary Stats"
"ag_detail_BaseStatsBody"	"レベルポイントを使うと、永久的に3種類の属性を上昇させられます。各属性の働きは異なります:\n\n- Strength はヘルスを上昇させ、Sven のような Strength 属性のヒーローの攻撃ダメージを追加します。\n- Agility はアーマーと攻撃速度を上昇させ、Luna のような Agility 属性のヒーローのダメージを追加します。\n- Intelligence は最高マナとマナ回復を上昇させ、Lina のような Intelligence 属性のヒーローの攻撃ダメージを追加します。"
"[english]ag_detail_BaseStatsBody"	"Level Points can also be spent to permanently increase all three of your attributes. Each attribute does something different:\n\n- Strength increases health, and adds attack damage for Strength heroes such as Sven.\n- Agility increases armor and attack speed, and adds attack damage for Agility heroes such as Luna.\n- Intelligence increases maximum mana and mana regeneration, and adds attack damage for Intelligence heroes such as Lina."
"ag_detail_InventoryTitle"	"インベントリ管理"
"[english]ag_detail_InventoryTitle"	"Managing Your Inventory"
"ag_detail_InventoryBody"	"新アイテムの為のスペースが無い状態になることもありえます。そんなときは、他のアイテムと併せることでより強力な別のアイテムに作り替えることが賢明です。\n\n合成可能なアイテムを持っていない場合には、ショップに行き、アイテムを右クリックして「売る」を選びましょう。"
"[english]ag_detail_InventoryBody"	"You may find yourself without inventory space for new items. The best way to clear space is to buy items which can be combined to create other, more powerful items.\n\nIf none of your items can be combined, you can sell an item by visiting any shop, right-clicking on what you wish to sell, and selecting \"Sell\"."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Power Treads - 高速移動と攻撃強化"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsTitle"	"Item Details: Power Treads - Faster Movement and Stronger Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsBody"	"ブーツは最も重要なアイテムの一つです。移送速度は相手を追いかけたり敵をかわしたりするのに欠かせません。\n\nPower Treads は攻撃速度を上昇させて Luna の強力な攻撃をサポートし、 上昇させたい第一属性を切り替えることができます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsBody"	"Boots are one of the most important items in the game. Movement speed is crucial for chasing down, or retreating from, an opponent.\n\nPower Treads complement Luna's high attack damage with increased attack speed, and can be activated to switch the primary attribute they increase."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Ring of Aquila - Agility 追加、ダメージ上昇など"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaTitle"	"Item Details: Ring of Aquila - Added Agility, Increased Damage, and More"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaBody"	"Luna の第一属性は Agility で、Wraith Band はAgility に手ごろなブーストを提供します。\n\nWraith Band は、ダメージ、マナ回復、アーマーを経済的に上昇することのできる Luna にピッタリの Ring of Aquila にアップグレードすることができます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaBody"	"Luna's primary attribute is Agility, and Wraith Band provides an affordable boost to Agility.\n\nUpgrading a Wraith Band into a Ring of Aquila is an economical way to add attack damage, mana regeneration, and armor, making this an excellent item for Luna."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Morbid Mask - 各攻撃で回復"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealTitle"	"Item Details: Morbid Mask - Healing with Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealBody"	"ヘルスを保つことは重要です。Morbid Mask はパッシブで、攻撃から受けるダメージを一部回復します。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealBody"	"Keeping your health up is very important. Morbid Mask passively heals you for a portion of the damage you deal with attacks."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Yasha - 速度と Agility 追加"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaTitle"	"Item Details: Yasha - Added Speed and Agility"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaBody"	"Yasha は移動速度へのかなりのブーストに加え、Luna の攻撃ダメージを上昇させる Agility を上昇させます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaBody"	"Yasha provides a considerable boost to attack and movement speed, and a lot of Agility, which increases Luna's attack damage."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Helm of the Dominator - ダメージ追加とクリープのコントロール"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmTitle"	"Item Details: Helm of the Dominator - Added Damage and Controlling Creeps"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmBody"	"Morbid Mask へのこのアップグレードで追加のダメージとアーマーが手に入ります。\n\nまた、Helm を有効化すれば指定した敵クリープを支配して完全にコントロールできるようになります。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmBody"	"This upgrade to the Morbid Mask provides additional damage and armor.\n\nAlso, activating the Helm allows you to Dominate a target enemy creep, granting you full control of that creep."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Manta Style - 大型ブーストとイリュージョン"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaTitle"	"Item Details: Manta Style - Major Boosts and Illusions"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaBody"	"Manta Style は Yasha より大きなボーナスを保証します。\n\nManta Style を有効化させると、敵をアタックすることができるあなたのヒーローのイリュージョン（コピー）を作ります。イリュージョンは、元々のヒーローより弱いです。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaBody"	"Manta Style grants larger bonuses than Yasha provides.\n\nActivating Manta Style creates two illusions, or copies, of your hero. These can be ordered to attack enemies. Illusions from any source are weaker than their source hero."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Black King Bar - スペル免疫"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBTitle"	"Item Details: Black King Bar - Immunity from Spells"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBBody"	"When Black King Bar を有効化すると、あなたのヒーローはほとんどの敵のアビリティから来るエフェクトと攻撃に対して無敵状態となります。しかしながら、有効化する毎に、無敵状態の持続時間が短縮されていきます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBBody"	"When Black King Bar is activated, your hero becomes completely immune to the effects and damage from most enemy abilities. However, with each activation, the duration of this immunity is decreased."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Butterfly - 大型ブーストと有益な回避"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyTitle"	"Item Details: Butterfly - Massive Boosts and Helpful Evasion"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyBody"	"Butterfly はダメージ、攻撃速度と Agility に大きなボーナスを提供し、回避によって敵はあなたを攻撃しにくくなります。\n\n有効化アビリティである Flutte は回避を犠牲にする代わりに即効性の追加移動速度を提供します。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyBody"	"Butterfly provides a huge bonus to damage, attack speed, and Agility, while the evasion it provides makes you harder to hit.\n\nIts activation ability, Flutter, trades away its evasion for a quick burst of additional movement speed."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Satanic - 各攻撃で回復上昇"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicTitle"	"Item Details: Satanic - Increased Healing with Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicBody"	"Satanic は大量の Strength を与え、これはLuna にとっては追加ヘルスを意味します。\n\nSatanic を有効化すると一時的に、受けるダメージよりも大きな生命吸収を獲得し戦闘中のヘルス回復に役立ちます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicBody"	"Satanic grants a large amount of Strength, which for Luna means more health.\n\nActivating Satanic temporarily increases its lifesteal to be higher than the damage you deal, making it a great way to refill your health during a fight."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Power Treads - 高速移動と攻撃強化"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsTitle"	"Item Details: Power Treads - Faster Movement and Stronger Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsBody"	"ブーツは最も重要なアイテムの一つです。移送速度は相手を追いかけたり敵をかわしたりするのに欠かせません。\n\nPower Treads は攻撃速度を上昇させて Sven の強力な攻撃をサポートし、 上昇させたい第一属性を切り替えることができます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsBody"	"Boots are one of the most important items in the game. Movement speed is crucial for chasing down, or retreating from, an opponent.\n\nPower Treads compliment Sven's high attack damage with increased attack speed, and can be activated to switch the primary attribute they increase."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Drum of Endurance - 有益なブースト"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsTitle"	"Item Details: Drum of Endurance - Helpful Boosts"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance はSven の Strength, Agility 及び Intelligence  を上昇させると同時に、周囲の味方ヒーローの攻撃速度と移動速度を上昇させます。これはチーム戦において非常に役立ちます。\n\nDrum of Endurance を有効化すると一時的に速度ボーナスが上昇します。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance provides an increase to Sven's strength, agility, and intelligence, while also boosting the attack and movement speed of Sven and nearby allied heroes. This makes it especially useful in a team fight.\n\nActivating the Drum will temporarily increase the speed bonuses."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Morbid Mask - 各攻撃で回復"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealTitle"	"Item Details: Morbid Mask - Healing With Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealBody"	"ヘルスを保つことは重要です。Morbid Mask はパッシブで、攻撃から受けるダメージを一部回復し、ヘルスの維持に貢献します。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealBody"	"Keeping your health up is very important. The Morbid Mask passively heals you for a portion of the damage you deal with attacks, making it easier to keep your health up."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenCritTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Crystalys - 追加ダメージ & クリティカルストライク"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenCritTitle"	"Item Details: Crystalys - Added Damage & Critical Strikes"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenCritBody"	"Crystalys は攻撃ダメージを大幅に上昇させます。また、2倍のダメージを与えるクリティカルストライクの可能性を提供します。Sven の Great Cleave アビリティ使用時に幸運にもクリティカルストライクが発動すれば、素早く戦局を変えることができます。\n\n通常、Crystalys はより強力な Daedalus を作成するために購入されます。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenCritBody"	"Crystalys provides a large boost to attack damage. It also gives each attack a chance to become a critical strike, which deals double damage. A lucky critical strike, combined with Sven's Great Cleave ability, can quickly turn the tide of battle.\n\nGenerally, Crystalys is purchased in order to build the more powerful Daedalus."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Mask of Madness - 対価を払っての攻撃"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskTitle"	"Item Details: Mask of Madness - Attack Damage at a Cost"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskBody"	"攻撃するごとに、Morbid Mask の回復アビリティに少量の上昇を提供し、 Mask of Madness は有効化することで強力な Berserk アビリティを発動します。\n\n有効化すると、Berserk によって、攻撃速度と移動速度が上昇しますが、受けるダメージが大きくなります。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskBody"	"Providing a small increase to Morbid Mask's ability to heal with each attack, Mask of Madness has a powerful activation ability: Berserk.\n\nWhen activated, Berserk significantly increases how quickly you attack and move. However, while active Berserk also causes you to take additional damage."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Platemail - 攻撃への抵抗"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailTitle"	"Item Details: Platemail - Resistance to Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailBody"	"アーマーの各点は効果的にヒーローが敵から受けられる攻撃の 6% を上昇させます。Platemail は Sven の先天的なアーマーに加えてパッシブでアーマーを追加し、 Warcry アビリティとの使用することで、そう簡単には倒されないようになります。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailBody"	"Each point of armor decreases how much damage a hero takes from enemy attacks by 6%. The armor from Platemail is passively added with Sven's innate armor and, if combined with his armor-granting Warcry ability, can make him extremely difficult to take down."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Hyperstone - 攻撃速度ブースト"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneTitle"	"Item Details: Hyperstone - Attack Speed Boost"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneBody"	"Hyperstone はヒーローの攻撃速度を大幅に上昇させます。\n\n既に大量の攻撃を与えるヒーローの攻撃速度を上昇することは敵の破壊に役立ちます。 Hyperstone は、いくつかの強力なアイテムの材料でもあります。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneBody"	"Hyperstone provides a major increase to a hero's attack speed.\n\nIncreasing the attack speed of a hero whose attacks already deal a lot of damage is a great way to destroy enemies. Hyperstone is also a component of several other powerful items."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Assault Cuirass - 攻撃速度とアーマーオーラ"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultTitle"	"Item Details: Assault Cuirass - Attack speed and Armor aura"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultBody"	"Assault Cuirass は攻撃速度を大幅に向上させ大量のアーマーを与える。\n\nパッシブで周囲の味方のアーマーと攻撃速度を上昇させ、敵のアーマーを減少させるので、戦場に持っていくにはもってこいのアイテム。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultBody"	"Assault Cuirass provides a significant boost to attack speed, and a lot of armor.\n\nIt also passively increases the armor and attack speed of nearby allies, while reducing the armor of nearby enemies, making it an excellent item to bring into battle."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Daedalus - 更なるダメージ & より大きなクリティカルストライク"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritTitle"	"Item Details: Daedalus - More Damage & Bigger Critical Strikes"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritBody"	"Daedalus は Crystalys をあらゆる面で向上させたアイテムです: 攻撃ダメージを大幅に上昇させ、Crystalys よりも更に強力なクリティカルストライクの可能性を提供します。\n\n少しの幸運と Sven's Great Cleave アビリティによって、一撃でチーム戦に終止符を打つことが出来るかもしれません。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritBody"	"Daedalus directly improves on Crystalys in every way: it provides a much larger boost to attack damage, while also giving each attack a chance to become a far stronger critical strike than Crystalys allows.\n\nWith a bit of luck, and Sven's Great Cleave ability, it is possible to end a team fight with a single attack."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Phase Boots - 手の届く攻撃ダメージ"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseTitle"	"Item Details: Phase Boots - Affordable Attack Damage"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseBody"	"ブーツが提供する追加の移動速度は敵を追跡したり、敵から逃げるのに重要です。\n\nPhase Boots は攻撃ダメージを大幅に上昇させ、Lina のラストヒット獲得をより簡単にします。更に、Phase Boots を有効化すると、クリープをヒーローの間をすり抜けることができるようになります。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseBody"	"The additional movement speed provided by boots is crucial for retreating from, or chasing down, an enemy.\n\nPhase Boots also provide a considerable boost to attack damage, making it easier for Lina to strike last hits. Additionally, activating Phase Boots allows you to walk through creeps and heroes."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Drum of Endurance - 有益なブースト"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsTitle"	"Item Details: Drum of Endurance - Helpful Boosts"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance はSven の Strength, Agility 及び Intelligence を上昇させ、Lina に追加の攻撃ダメージを提供しての戦闘での生き残りをサポートします。Lina と周囲の味方ヒーローの攻撃速度と移動速度を上昇させます。\n\nDrum of Endurance を有効化すると一時的に速度ボーナスが上昇します。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance provides an increase to strength, agility, and intelligence, helping Lina to stay alive in battle while providing her with additional attack damage. It also increases the attack and move speed of Lina and nearby allied heroes.\n\nActivating the Drum will temporarily increase the speed bonuses."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Eul's Scepter of Divinity - 移動性と汎用性"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneTitle"	"Item Details: Eul's Scepter of Divinity - Mobility and Versatility"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneBody"	"Scepter of Divinity は Intelligence とマナ回復を提供し、Lina がより頻繁にアビリティを使用できるようにします。移動速度を上昇させ、Phase Boots と共に Fiery Soul のパッシブアビリティと良く調和します。\n\nCyclone アビリティは、少し離れた場所にいる敵を短時間空中に打ち上げます。Light Strike Array の爆発と着地のタイミングを合わせてみましょう！"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneBody"	"Scepter of Divinity provides intelligence and mana regeneration, allowing Lina to cast her abilities more often. Its increases to movement speed also pair well with Phase Boots and her Fiery Soul passive ability.\n\nIts Cyclone ability briefly traps a distant enemy in the air. Try to time a Light Strike Array to explode as they land!"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Soul Booster - ヘルスをマナ追加"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterTitle"	"Item Details: Soul Booster - Added Health & Mana"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterBody"	"Soul Booster は大量の追加ヘルスとヘルス回復をもたらし、Lina のような脆弱なヒーローのサポートに非常に役立ちます。マナとマナ回復を提供して、Lina がより頻繁にスペルを使用できるようにします。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterBody"	"Soul Booster provides a lot of additional health, plus health regeneration, which is extremely useful for a fragile hero like Lina. It also adds mana and mana regeneration, allowing Lina to cast her spells more often."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Octarine Core - キャスト向上"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineTitle"	"Item Details: Octarine Core - Improved Casting"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineBody"	"Octarine Core は Soul Booster をあらゆる面で向上させ、ヘルス、マナと回復を高める。大幅な Inteligence  を提供し、Lina のマナを更に上昇させ、攻撃ダメージを追加する。\n\n更に、キャスターがアビリティによって受けたダメージの一部をパッシブで回復し、 全てのクールダウンタイマーを減らす。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineBody"	"Octarine Core improves on Soul Booster in every way, providing more health, mana, and regeneration. It also provides a major boost to intelligence, further increasing Lina's mana while adding attack damage.\n\nAdditionally, it passively heals the caster for a portion of any damage dealt by abilities, and reduces all cooldown timers."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBTitle"	"アイテム詳細: Monkey King Bar - ダメージ上昇"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBTitle"	"Item Details: Monkey King Bar - Increased Damage"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBBody"	"Monkey King Bar はダメージを大幅に向上させ、更に一定確率で各攻撃にボーナスダメージとミニスタンを与える Bash と、敵ヒーローあるいはクリープへの攻撃が必ず当たるようにする True Strike という 二つの恩恵をもたらす。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBBody"	"Monkey King Bar grants a major boost to damage, plus two additional benefits: Bash, which causes each attack to have a chance to deal bonus damage along with an interrupting mini-stun, and True Strike, which ensures that every attack against an enemy hero or creep will hit its target."
"ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingTitle"	"アビリティ: Lunar Blessing - 攻撃ブースターと夜間視力"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingTitle"	"Ability: Lunar Blessing - Attack Booster and Night Vision"
}
